Lowell Thomas Papers
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Subject Files
1.2.3
Marist Archives and Special Collections
  482
  - American Emergency Committee for Tibetan Refugees (AECTR), 1959 April 28 - 1980 May; 3
  - Bibliography on Tibet, 1950; 4
  - Daniel Bragg: notes on the Tibetan broadcasts, 1949 August - October; 5
  - Bureau of His Holiness the Dalai Lama, 1961 August 4 - 1967 September 9; 6
  - Central Relief Committee (India), circa 1961; 7
  - Central Relief Committee (India), circa 1961; 8
  - Coins [see oversize box TOS-1 for original coins], circa 1949; 9
  - Conspiracy theories, 1966; 10
  - Customs, 1949 September 1 - November 4; 11
  - Electra Ward Nicks, 1981 July - August; 12
  - The Encyclopedia Americana, 1954 March - 1963; 13
  483
  - Equipment and supplies, 1949 - 1950; 1
  - Flight from Tibet, 1959 June 3; 2
  - Game of Sho, 1957 May 13; 3
  - High Adventure with Lowell Thomas in Tibet, circa 1957 - 1959; 4
  - High Adventure with Lowell Thomas in Tibet, circa 1957 - 1959; 5
  - High Adventure with Lowell Thomas in Tibet, circa 1957 - 1959; 6
  - Mission Rescue: Adventuring for Christ from Tibet to Burma told by LaVerne Morse to Dorothy Fay Foster (picture story), 1946; 7
  - Notes, undated; 8
  - Office of Tibet, 1961 May 26 - 1981 December 30; 9
  - Receipts, 1949; 10
  - Sketches, undated; 11
  - Tenki Tenduf-La, 1951; 12
  - Gyalo Thondup, undated; 13
  - The Tibet Society, 1967 January - February 7; 14
  - Tibet Trade Mission (business cards), circa 1949; 15
  - Tibetan Bulletin, 1978 March - April; 16
  - Tibetan frontier pass for Lowell Thomas and Lowell Thomas, Jr., 1949 August 5 - 27 October; 17
  484
  - Tibetan Homes Foundation, 1963 July 4 - 1975 May 28; 1
  - Tibetan Industrial Rehabilitation Society (TIRS), 1970 April 6 - May 19; 2
  - Tibetan postage stamps, circa 1949; 3
  - Tibetan recordings, 1949 - 1954 January 28; 4
  - Tibetan review, 1978 April, May, December; 5
  - Tibetan scroll presented to President Harry Truman, 1949 November 9; 6
  - Tibetan skit, circa late 1950s; 7
  - Tibetan students, 1951 - 1970; 8
  - Travel arrangements, 1949; 9
  - The University Museum (University of Pennsylvania), 1949 August - November; 10
  485
  - Tibetan Homes Foundation, 1963 July 4 - 1975 May 28; 1
  - Tibetan Industrial Rehabilitation Society (TIRS), 1970 April 6 - May 19; 2
  - Tibetan postage stamps, circa 1949; 3
  - Tibetan recordings, 1949 - 1954 January 28; 4
  - Tibetan review, 1978 April, May, December; 5
  - Tibetan scroll presented to President Harry Truman, 1949 November 9; 6
  - Tibetan skit, circa late 1950s; 7
  - Tibetan students, 1951 - 1970; 8
  - Travel arrangements, 1949; 9
  - The University Museum (University of Pennsylvania), 1949 August - November; 10